<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent" >

    <RelativeLayout
        android:id="@+id/relativeLayout1"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
        android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true" >

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView1"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
            android:layout_centerVertical="true"
            android:text="Help"
            android:textSize="25sp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/help_close"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
            android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginRight="5dp"
            android:text="X"
            android:textColor="#FF0000"
            android:textSize="28sp" />

    </RelativeLayout>

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView1"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
        android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
        android:layout_below="@+id/relativeLayout1" >

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:orientation="vertical" >

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView2"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Stat Lookup: If you&apos;d like to look up information about a team specifically, use the team lookup. If you&apos;d like to look up information about a game, on the other hand, use the game lookup. \nThere&apos;s easy navigation from one to the other in the dropdown menu. \nFrom there, select a sport, and as you do so, the title at the top will dictate what to do next.\nNote: some teams may not be available (Non-FBS college football teams, Canadian baseball team in spring training...etc.). \n\nOptions will only appear if the previous one is set. Generally speaking, the sport is listed as SPORT: LEAGUE (LOCATION) with sport, then location, in alphabetical order. Use that fact to help navigate. \n\nOnce you have set all of the options, hit submit.\n\nStatWell: The StatWell is where most of the information will appear. There&apos;s an option in the menu that will allow you to decide what type of information you&apos;d like inside the StatWell, selecting from the given options. The content is somewhat interactive -- for example, press and hold a URL to open it up in a web page, and email to send one to that target.\n\nPlayer Search: Once the full set of options are set and you have successfully looked up data for a team/game, the player search option also becomes available.\n\nTwitter/Facebook: See something interesting, and feel like sharing? There&apos;s Twitter and Facebook integration. Once you click the menu option for facebook, you log in (if it&apos;s your first time using it), and then you can post a status.Twitter works similarly, except instead of a status you send a tweet. \nAdditionally, if you feel like seeing what public perception of a player/team is, through Facebook, there&apos;s an option to search public posts, and through Twitter public tweets.\n\nAdditional Help: Finally, if you see a ? anywhere, if you click that, a pop up will appear giving you more information."
                android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</RelativeLayout>